Falling down a bottomless pit is boring
'cause it's taking SO LONG!
Blocky, I see the bottom of this pit.
"Bottomless" is such a lie.
A lie?
What? There's a bottom?
Oh, my tree, I see spikes!
AAAAAAAAA!
Need some money fast and soon?
Then buy our Box of Paper Slips!
At first it might just seem like a blank slip of paper,
but you can scribble a number on it, and POOF!
It's a dollar bill!
This person managed to buy a TV.
This person bought a house!
This person bought the world!
So, yeah! BUY NOW!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAA!
Huh?
Hey, it's Spongy!
AAAAAA!
SPONGY:
Bueeuuugh-OOO!!
AAAAAAAAA!
Hey, it's you!
Yes, it's me. And I have to tell you that your team,
the SquAHshy Grapes, lost last episode's contest.
Go that way to the Cake at Stake place.
Walk! Run! Jog! Walk! Run! Jog! Walk! Run! Jog! Walk! Run! Jog!
♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Subtitles: Daniel Adam Valle
I am so glad to see that we're no longer the losers!
Yeah, well, Bubble, you almost made us lose.
So don't do that again.
We're getting close.
Halt.
Since this is a new stage in
the Battle for Dream Island,
we need to renovate the Cake at Stake place.
[TA-DA!]
That's all you can afford to do?
No. There's more.
[TA-DA!]
Wow! Ooh! Wow! Ooh, wooow, that's amazing!
Oh, my gosh! That's amazing! Woooah!
So, yeah, sit.
Squashy!
♪ Hork hork hork, glorp glorp ♪
♪ Gloop gloop gloop, doot doot ♪
♪ Cake at Stake! ♪
This time, we got twenty-nine votes.
As you know, the three of you with the fewest votes
receive a slice of cake, and will stay in the game.
The other two will leave the team.
However, the winning team will choose
one of the two onto their team.
Let's start.
Blocky, do you want to use your Win Token?
No! I just got this thingy last episode!
Ok, then.
At the lowest, with one vote, is Ice Cube.
Wha?
Hey! That's not cake!
That's modeling clay!
The cake was too expensive.
Blocky, you're safe at two votes.
Yeah!
ANNOUNCER:
Leafy, Teardrop, and Snowball,
only one of you is safe.
and that person happens
to be Leafy, with three votes.
Yes! Whaaa?
ANNOUNCER:
Teardrop and Snowball...
you got five and eighteen votes respectively.
Come with me.
Well, guys, we may be a little smaller,
but we're still the best team ever!
ANNOUNCER:
Snowball and Teardrop,
the Squishy Cherries will either vote
you onto their team or to be eliminated.
So Eraser, please pick.
I want Snowball on my team!
He's just AWESOME!
Well, Snowball's not so smart,
so I'll say Teardrop!
OMG, I so totally, like, agree.
I choose Teardrop. SB is totally a jerk.
No, I think SB is...
is AWESOME!
Oh, so it's all down to me.
Uhhhgh...
Uh, well...
Snowball won contests four and five, so I pick him.
Teardrop, it's time to say goodbye.
Yeah! Still in it to WIN IT!
So now it is down to the final fourteen.
The tenth contest is a crying contest.
Fill your tubs as high as you can with tears.
Ehhh, EH! EH, EH!
EHH!!!
Eraser, you're not crying!
Crying is for WIMPS!
Snowball? You, too!?
WHY should I TRY to CRY?!
Oh, no!
HEUGH-
CRYYYIIING!
HEUUUGH-
Oh, oh, no, OH,
NOOO!!!
Uh...so?
Don't you know, Coiny?
Crying? Tears?
Water is my POISON!
Sorry! I forgot!
Try to cry!
Okay.
EEEEEHHH!
Not a drop! I'll try.
ULEGEUGHAUGHEUAGLUGAUGALAGUHUAHGYGHAG!
Yeah! Low five!
Hey, let's melt Icy!
Heegh...HYUP!
Heh?
[GASP] That was mean!
That was MEAN!
Boop. Time's up!
Since you all got some water, I guess it's a tie.
No fair! Look how much water we ha-
The tiebreaker is a skiing contest.
Hey, Match, look!
It's mini-Snowball!
Ooh, I'll get my mini-Match.
Let's play Spongy Cake!
People, try to get to the finish ASAP.
Oh, and we could only afford
one pair of skis for each team.
What?
Go.
Oh, my gosh!
Ready?
Huh? Not quite...
I still don't like what you did to Icy.
Hey! The Ice Cube Recovery Center
will make Ice Cube alive again!
Still!
- How's it going?
- Uh, wobbly!
Hey, where's Rocky?
There!
WEAAAAUUUUUGH!!!!
Three, two, one, JUMP!
Which is which?
I don't know!
Icy!
Well, it's pretty obvious that
Leafy and Blocky got second place,
but I'm not sure which of the other two
teams were in first place or third place,
so we need another tiebreaker.
Aw, seriously?
It is a handstand contest.
When I press the button, the ropes will release
If you are the last one handstanding,
your team wins, and you get a Win Token.
The other team is in dead last.
Go.
Bleh!
Ha-ha!
Another Name has already lost.
The Cherries win again, but who will get the Win Token?
Bleh!
Whoooaaaa! Oh, oh, no! Oh, nooo! Whoaaa!
HEUUUGH! Habubabubabah! Heeuuugh oh, nooo!
Huu! Huuu!! HUUU!! HUUUUU!
HUU! HUUU! HUU! HUU!
ANNOUNCER:
Eraser gets his second Win Token.
YEAH!
ANNOUNCER:
You can only use one at a time.
AWH!
ANNOUNCER:
The Cherries go to first, and the Names to last.
Voters, choose one member of Another Name to leave BFDI.
TB, GB, Rocky, Coiny or Firey.
The two most voted will leave the team.
One will join the Cherries.
Would you look at that? My very first tear!
I'll always remember this for the rest of my life.